<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Powerpak &#8211; Mobile Solar</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/tag/powerpak/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.mobilesolarpower.net</link>
	<description>Solar Generators and Light Towers</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Thu, 19 May 2022 15:31:30 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.13</generator>
	<item>
		<title>On Mobile Solar’s 10th Anniversary Elon Musk brings Energy Storage to the Mainstream!</title>
		<link>https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/on-mobile-solars-10th-anniversary-elon-musk-brings-energy-storage-to-the-mainstream/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 21:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[T S]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[backup power]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Solar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobile solar generator]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Powerpak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solar power]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/?p=1905</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Exactly 10 years ago, Mobile Solar created its first trailer-based solar generator. Coupling solar panels and batteries was a very novel concept at the time and as the years went on we became increasingly enthusiastic about the possibility of a future in which the sun ...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/on-mobile-solars-10th-anniversary-elon-musk-brings-energy-storage-to-the-mainstream/">On Mobile Solar’s 10th Anniversary Elon Musk brings Energy Storage to the Mainstream!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net">Mobile Solar</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exactly 10 years ago, Mobile Solar created its first trailer-based solar generator. Coupling solar panels and batteries was a very novel concept at the time and as the years went on we became increasingly enthusiastic about the possibility of a future in which the sun could provide us with energy at all hours of the day. The success of our units have proven the utility of such a system but we realize that we can only do so much with our transportable units that cater to a small and largely to off-grid clientele.<br />
For years we have waited for GE, Edison or some major utility to offer a large scale renewable energy storage solution. Yesterday such a solution was brought to the mainstream by Elon Musk’s Tesla, one of the most forward thinking companies on the planet.  Tesla’s new battery systems, the Powerwall and the Powerpack will be tremendously crucial to our renewable energy powered future. Excess solar power produced during the day can now be stored for later use in an economical way like never before.<br />
We look forward to a solar powered future and the possibility of using Tesla’s new batteries in our future units.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/on-mobile-solars-10th-anniversary-elon-musk-brings-energy-storage-to-the-mainstream/">On Mobile Solar’s 10th Anniversary Elon Musk brings Energy Storage to the Mainstream!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net">Mobile Solar</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
