<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>disaster recovery &#8211; Mobile Solar</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/tag/disaster-recovery/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.mobilesolarpower.net</link>
	<description>Solar Generators and Light Towers</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Thu, 19 May 2022 15:31:30 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.13</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Mobile Solar and OutBack Power Team Up to Provide Quick Solar Power Solutions for Japan’s Tsunami Disaster Area</title>
		<link>https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/mobile-solar-and-outback-power-team-up-to-provide-quick-solar-power-solutions-for-japans-tsunami-disaster-area/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 15:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[T S]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[disaster recovery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japanese Tsunami]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Solar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile solar power. solar power generators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outback Power]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/?p=1088</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Arlington, WA – May 9, 2011- OutBack Power Technologies, Inc. and their integration partner, Mobile Solar, have responded to a request to support power requirements needed since the recent tsunami in the hard hit Sendai area of Japan.  Using OutBack’s GFX3024J model inverters with 120VAC ...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/mobile-solar-and-outback-power-team-up-to-provide-quick-solar-power-solutions-for-japans-tsunami-disaster-area/">Mobile Solar and OutBack Power Team Up to Provide Quick Solar Power Solutions for Japan’s Tsunami Disaster Area</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net">Mobile Solar</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Arlington, WA – May 9, 2011- </strong>OutBack Power Technologies, Inc. and their integration partner, Mobile Solar, have responded to a request to support power requirements needed since the recent tsunami in the hard hit Sendai area of Japan.  Using OutBack’s GFX3024J model inverters with 120VAC 50Hz output, Mobile Solar built and shipped a total of six MS-150 model solar generators in the first phase of a large deployment.  Upon arrival, the units were immediately outfitted with water purification systems and construction tools to allow workers to rebuild residential neighborhoods.</p>
<p><strong> </strong>Travis Semmes, President of Mobile Solar, said “we have chosen OutBack Power as our technology partner on the inverter/charger and charge controller side.  OutBack has proven a perfect match for our product line and our customers’ needs – supplying a consistently reliable and durable product that gets the job done.  With this in mind, we knew we could provide an effective, high quality mobile solar generator solution for the victims of the recent tsunami.”</p>
<p>“We are glad to have been given the opportunity to work with Mobile Solar to help provide these units for this important application” said Glenn Baker, OutBack’s Vice President of Sales.  “Our technology has been deployed worldwide to provide an efficient way to get power to remote locations and this quick response is due in no small part to our close partnership with Mobile Solar”, added Baker.</p>
<p><strong>Mobile Solar</strong>, based in Atascadero, CA, was founded in 2006 with the mission of designing and building portable, solar electric solutions, or “solar generators”.  They are off-grid configurations that take the place of traditional generators, outputting clean, quiet and reliable power to a wide variety of applications.  Mobile Solar is the leading industry OEM in the portable, off-grid PV market.  Mobile Solar was the first to bring a full solar generator product lineup to market.  For this and/or additional information in electronic form, go to <a href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/">www.mobilesolarpower.net</a>.</p>
<p><strong>OutBack Power Technologies, Inc.</strong> manufactures innovative power conversion solutions that integrate solar, wind and hydro resources to provide reliable electric power for the renewable energy, mobile and backup power markets. OutBack Power&#8217;s engineers have decades of power conversion electronics design and equipment installation experience and share a passion for leading the industry into a new era of performance, ease of use, durability, and standardization.  OutBack Power is a member of The Alpha Group.  For this and/or additional information in electronic form, go to <a href="http://www.outbackpower.com/">www.outbackpower.com</a>.</p>
<p><strong>The Alpha Group</strong> represents a global alliance of independent companies that share a common philosophy &#8211; create world-class powering solutions for communication, commercial, industrial and renewable energy markets.  For this and/or additional information in electronic form, go to <a href="http://www.alpha.com/">www.alpha.com</a>.</p>
<p>For more information contact:</p>
<p>Travis Semmes                                                                         John M. Grubb<br />
President, Mobile Solar                                                         V. P., Marketing, Alpha Technologies<br />
(805) 466-1006                                                                        (360) 392-2331<br />
<a href="mailto:travis@mobilesolarpower.net">travis@mobilesolarpower.net</a>                                               <a href="mailto:jgrubb@alpha.com">jgrubb@alpha.com</a></p>
<p>Take a look at Outback Power&#8217;s Website at <a title="Outback Power" href="http://www.outbackpower.com/news/article/65/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">http://www.outbackpower.com/news/article/65/</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net/mobile-solar-and-outback-power-team-up-to-provide-quick-solar-power-solutions-for-japans-tsunami-disaster-area/">Mobile Solar and OutBack Power Team Up to Provide Quick Solar Power Solutions for Japan’s Tsunami Disaster Area</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mobilesolarpower.net">Mobile Solar</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
